

Contacts

Pilsen, Czech Republic +420 736 746 211 (CR) +380 994 091 743 (UA) malyk.vitaliy@gmail.com <u>Telegram</u> <u>GitHub</u> LinkedIn

Tech skills

- HTML5/CSS3
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- JavaScript
- GITHub
- Parcel
- Webpack
- REST API
- React
- Redux Toolkit
- TypeScript
- Node.js
- Express
- MongoDB

Soft skills

- Operations management
- Staff development
- Negotiation
- Critical thinking
- Team work
- Analytics skills

Languages

- Ukrainian Native
- Czech Intermediate
- English Pre-Intermediate
- Russian Native

Vitalii Malyk

Junior frontend developer

Summary

I am a Frontend developer with knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React. I have experience using Agile/Scrum methodology to successfully deliver projects on time, on budget and with a focus on user experience. I am very passionate about programming, especially when I can help make a positive difference, both in my everyday life and in business.

Project experience

Phonebook, Link [React, Redux Toolkit, JS, CSS, JS] Adaptive application. Position: developer. I created the project using React and the Redux Toolkit.

Film library, Link [React, JS, CSS, HTML5]

Adaptive application. Position: developer. I created a project using React and and hooks.

TastyTreats, Link [HTML, CSS, JS]

Adaptive site layout on vanilla JavaScript. Position: developer.

Wristwatch, Link [HTML, CSS, JS]

Responsive layout website. Position: Scrum Master, developer. We created a project on Github, checked for assembly and site errors.

Work experience

LLC "BudInvest", Ukraine (oct 2016 - feb 2022)

Deputy General Director for Construction

- Conclusion of construction contracts
- Organization of the work of the construction department of the company
- Checking the budget documentation

LLC "DISK", Ukraine (feb 2013 - sep 2016)

Civil engineer - Department head

- Construction calculations
- Calculation of the cost of work
- Organization of construction

Education

2023

IT School GoIT Full Stack Developer

2005 - 2010

Donbas Academy of Construction and Architecture Civil engineer